The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The Heng Yue Sect...
The country of Zhao...
Teng Family...
To avenge my family,
you will pay
with your life !
400 years
passed by in the blink of an eye.
It may not be a long time
for cultivators.
-But for mortals,
it's multiple lifetimes.
The wood carvings of the Immortals
will influence the protection they provide our country.
These carvings must have
outstanding form and spirit.
No matter what you have done,
you have to take care of yourself.
That way,
your parents can rest in peace.
Noooo !!!
Father,
Mother,
Tie Zhu is back.
Your unfilial son Wang Lin
swears an oath today.
I will make the Teng Family pay blood for blood !
It's so cold.
What ?
Wang Liao Yi
Wang Family descendant
Someone came ?
Why is it so cold today ?
Who are you ?
Why are you in the Wang family's ancestral home ?
What's your relationship with the tablets ?
I am Wang Liao Yi.
My ancestor Wang Tian Tu
was the fourth brother of the person on the tablet.
Fourth Uncle ?
When the ancestor was middle aged,
he was spotted by an Immortal of the Piao Miao Sect.
He became a vassal of the royal family after leaving the mountains.
That's the story of our branch of the Wang family.
Fourth Uncle's descendants are alive.
This is a blessing for the Wang Family.
What's this ?
Why is her Spirit Root missing ?
Everyone is born with a Spirit Root
but they all have different properties.
Their quality
determines the potential for cultivation.
To become a so-called "Immortal"
we cultivate and absorb
spiritual energy from the world.
The mortals
will only rely on the energy their Spirit Root had at birth
during their whole life.
What will happen if a mortal doesn't have one ?
If a mortal loses their Spirit Root
they will become sick
and heavily lose weight.
This is definitely not simple.
Do you remember when
you started to get sick ?
I don't remember.
The health of the family is very poor.
We consulted doctors,
but they didn't find anything.
My illness is mild.
I'm afraid that the Wang family offended a cultivator
that stole the family's Spirit Roots.
In all my life,
my body has never felt so light.
Thank you Immortal !
By the way,
I should be your ancestor.
Our Wang family has an Immortal ancestor ?
Thanks to Fourth Uncle,
I successfully became an Immortal
so I will protect his descendants
to repay his kindness.
Come.
Where to ?
The capital,
to the Wang family.
Country of Zhao
Who's coming ?
Wang ?
Two people ?
Yes.
Come in.
My Lord,
have mercy on us.
Please let us leave.
You don't meet the conditions.
I can't let you pass.
Go away !
Why is it so hard to leave the city ?
Immortal doesn't know,
the government is afraid that if someone leaves they will not come back.
Therefore, those who don't have a family to protect
cannot leave the city.
How was the mortals' capital of Zhao
reduced to this ?
Not a single person here has a Spirit Root...
Miss,
you are finally back.
The patriarch... he will not make it.
Grandfather...
Grandfather !
Yi'er is back.
Wang Zefu
Wang Family Patriarch
Please look at me once more !
Indeed,
missing a Spirit Root for too long
will result in death.
Immortal.
Please,
please save my grandfather...
Save him ?
He can save him ?
He can save the patriarch ?
He's really an Immortal ?
Magic powers ?
The patriarch is saved !
Yes !
The patriarch is awake !
Grandfather,
Grandfather !
This is...
I didn't think
our Wang family had a living Immortal ancestor.
We are truly blessed.
Don't worry about it.
Immortal ancestor must want to know...
Decades ago, after changes occured in the Immortal world,
the people of Zhao all caught an illness.
I know it's not a plague
but I don't know the true cause.
Alright,
since I owe Fourth Uncle,
I will help you.
Formation, activate !
The trees in the garden are growing leaves !
I can feel the energy !
It's relaxing.
Madam. Your hair is turning black.
Dear, your back is straight again !
Yes.
This formation is called the Spirit Gathering Formation.
It will protect the Wang family around it.
Thank you Immortal.
We are truly grateful.
Wait ! It's me !
Zhang Kuang
Tiandao Sect Disciple
Qi Condensation
I'm Zhang Kuang of the Heng Yue Sect,
please enlighten me.
Senior Brother Zhang Kuang ?
I recognized you when you entered the city,
but wanted to confirm
so I followed you.
In what condition is the Heng Yue Sect ?
I haven't gone back in years.
Senior Brother Zhang, why are you in the capital ?
And your cultivation...
The spiritual energy in your body is scattered
and your meridians are very fragile.
I followed the Heng Yue Ancestors.
After many years of cultivation,
I reached Core Formation.
I went down the mountain
to gain experience.
I hoped for a breakthrough
to restore the glory of the Heng Yue Sect.
But it didn't go as planned.
I was captured by the Tiandao Sect.
They used my body to refine pills.
My...
My lifelong cultivation has gone to waste.
Now, I can only be exploited as a disciple.
There are 7 pills in it.
You will take one per month,
and in 7 months
you will have recovered at least half your cultivation.
Senior Brother Zhang, take care.
I hope that
we will see each other again.
Wait...
Wait a minute.
Do not investigate
the disappearance of Spirit Roots.
Does the Tiandao Sect have something to do with it ?
The less you know, the better.
The Tiandao Sect is cruel,
but they would not dare to steal Spirit Roots of mortals.
I fear that
there must be someone else involved.
If you interfere,
they will find out !
They are coming !
You dare to make a Spirit Gathering Formation behind my back ?
Are you tired of living ?
Who did it ?
Lu Shiming
Tiandao Sect Elder
Late stage Core Formation
Speak !
Hide inside,
I will take care of this.
Thank you Immortal !
Hurry up !
Did you do it ?
You dare to act like this on our Tiandao Sect's territory ?
You really have a death wish !
We are all cultivators,
let's discuss this.
Please give me some face.
Elder Lu,
Brother Wang set the formation to protect his descendants.
It will not affect the sect's plans.
Who do you think you are ?
You think we can talk this out ?
You dare to attack in the Tiandao Sect's territory ?
Do you want to make an enemy of the Teng Family !?
Teng ?
The Tiandao Sect is backed by the Teng Family !
I'm not afraid to tell you that
the mortals' land also belongs to the Teng Family !
Go !
This is bad !
It's the Fallen Souls Devouring Formation.
Any counsciousness trapped in it will be devoured.
Their Divine Sense will shatter
and they will fall to madness.
Xu Liguo...
I am here !
This is great !
I haven't eaten in a long time !
It will be delicious.
That's it ?
You couldn't even fill the gaps between my teeth.
How is it possible ?
You...
Who the hell are you !?
You mentionned the Teng Family...
I haven't even begun
yet you come to me yourself...
You can't kill me.
If you do, you will offend both the Tiandao Sect and the Teng Family.
Do you dare ?
You...
You're going to destroy the Tiandao Sect ?
I will not stop
at just the Tiandao Sect.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.